保持呼吸
Keep breathing.
平平稳稳地
Nice and slow.
头几枪会告诉你
Now, the first couple of shots
枪准星准不准
will show you if the sights are off
枪管直不直
or the barrel's bent.
我和你直说了吧
Let me make this real easy for you.
准星不准  枪管也不直
The sights are off and the barrel's bent.
你偏左了大约一英寸
Mm, you're off to the left about an inch.
对  绕着那星星打
That's it. Shoot around the star.
而不是瞄着它
Not at it.
-成功  -太好了  你成功了
- Yes! - Yeah! You did it!
我一个人可做不到
I didn't.
你给你女友赢了一个泰迪熊
You just won your girlfriend a teddy bear.
太好了  你说她会最喜欢哪个
Cool. Hey, which one you think she'd like best?
然后周四晚上
And then Thursday night,
这个物理学家会在布鲁克林演讲
this physicist is giving a lecture in Brooklyn.
是关于时间旅行和祖父悖论的
It's about time travel and the grandfather paradox.
我不知道你有没有空
I don't know if you're busy...
亨利  亨利
Okay, Henry. Henry...um...
我们能谈谈么
Can we talk for a second?
行啊
Yeah.
咱们能经常一起出来我很开心
I'm really happy that we've been hanging out so much.
对  我也挺喜欢你的
Yeah, I-- I like you too.
你能把那熊先放下吗
Can you put down the bear?
亨利
Henry...
怎么了
What?
我做不到
I can't.
我知道
I know.
你是有女友的
You have a girlfriend.
只是...
It's just...
她好像从来...
she never seems...
不愿意跟你一起外出
to want to do anything with you.
你哭了吗
Are you crying?
没有  我会过敏
No, I have allergies.
肯定是这样  我才流泪的
I must just be, like, tearing up.
亨利  那好像是血啊
Henry, I think that's blood.
什么  这...
What? I--it...
总监：
zlean
三十五岁男子哭出了血
35-year-old male cries blood,
但他不是吸血鬼比尔
and he's not vampire Bill.
《真爱如血》男主角吸血鬼比尔
该剧中所有吸血鬼流的都是血泪
开始
Go!
我们应该提问吗
Should we ask?
不该
Nope!
问她吗
What, her?
是这样  我最喜欢的伴侣
Yeah, my favorite companion
不再给人当伴侣了
is retiring from "companning."
所以我在面试她的接班人
So I'm interviewing replacements.
谢谢你
Thank you...
黄油威士忌小姐
Butterscotch.
这是你的姓吗
Is that a family name?
你准备在这办公室玩多久的性爱游戏
How long are you gonna be using the office for sex games?
好让我安排一下我的一天
Just so I can plan my day.
边做爱边工作吗
Sex and work?
我又不是野蛮人
I'm not a savage.
我要的是卡布奇诺
I asked for a cappuccino.
这就是
That's what this is.
不对  卡布奇诺上面有漂亮的泡沫
No, a cappuccino's got a nice, stiff foam on it.
这要湿过
This is wetter than...
差点说漏嘴了
Oh... almost slipped there.
谢谢你
Well, thank you,
威士忌小姐
Ms. Scotch,
但是你这咖啡泡沫打得太差了
but poor foaming's a deal breaker.
你能叫下一个候选人进来吗
Could you ask the next candidate to come in?
初次检查显示无外伤征象
Initial exam showed no sign of trauma
也没有球结膜下出血
or subconjunctival hemorrhage.
淋巴细胞增多症
Lymphocytosis?
淋巴细胞绝对计数在正常范围
Alc's in normal range,
但结果位于正常范围上限
but it's in the high end of normal.
请坐  媚娘
Take a seat, Fawn.
回答我  你最喜欢的伍迪·艾伦电影是哪部
And tell me, what's your favorite Woody Allen movie?
《安妮·霍尔》
Annie Hall.
你面试妓女
You're interviewing hookers
却不问她们有关性的问题吗
but not gonna talk to them about sex?
性是给定的
Sex is a given.
她们可是妓女啊
They're hookers.
解释一下你的答案
Defend your choice.
这部名气最大
It's the most popular.
就差这么一点
Ohh...that's so close.
我们可以接受"黛安·基顿穿西装很好看'
We would have accepted, "Diane Keaton looks great in suits,"
或是"这是对现今社会道德观念的一种抨击"
or, "It's a trenchant commentary on today's mores,"
或是"我想吃鸡蛋"
or, "I needed the eggs."
谢谢你来应聘
Thanks for your interest.
想要被我雇佣  应招女郎
To get the gig, call girl--
抱歉  是应招妇女
sorry, call woman--
要会些既实用
needs a combination of skills
又好玩的技能
that I find useful/entertaining
这样我花一小时的钱
for the remaining 57 minutes
除去做爱剩下57分钟还有事可干
of the hour I paid for.
淋巴细胞增多症能解释的通
Lymphocytosis works.
也许我们应该再去验验血
Maybe we should take another look at the blood.
也可能是海绵窦血栓形成
Could also be cavernous sinus thrombosis.
血凝块引起颅内压增高
Clot builds up pressure at the base of the brain.
重测血小板
Rerun the patient's blood panel
再做头颅CT静脉造影检查
and get a CT venogram of his head.
到时候看谁说的对
Let's see which one of you is right.
你修理小家电的手艺怎么样
How are you with small appliance repair?
这个海绵窦血栓  会造成生命危险吗
Uh, this cavernous sinus thing, is it dangerous?
如果亨利得的是这病
If Henry's got it,
我们可以通过手术和药物同时进行治疗
we can treat it with a combo of drugs and surgery.
成功率在七成以上
Success rate is over 70%.
你要我再给艾米打个电话吗
Do you want me to call Amy again?
不用了  没事的
No, it's fine.
艾米是他女朋友
Amy's his girlfriend.
我是他邻居
I'm the neighbor.
我给他们的电话里留言了
I did leave a message at their number.
你要不要试试打她手机
Do you wanna try her cell?
你至少得在这待上几小时
Be here for a few more hours at least.
她没手机  她害怕辐射
Oh, she doesn't have one. She worries about radiation.
我可以顺路给她带个话
I could stop by on my way home.
她知道我是谁  对吗
She knows who I am, right?
不用了  但还是谢谢你
You don't need to, but thanks.
祝你好运
Good luck.
好的
Okay.
你招过妓吗
Have you ever paid for sex?
每个看过莫谦特艾佛利电影的男人
Every guy who's ever seen a Merchant Ivory movie
著名电影双人组合
制片伊斯玛·莫谦特和导演詹姆斯·艾佛利组成的电影公司
都招过妓
has paid for sex.
没有
No.
这种行为..
It just...
是对女性极大的不尊重
seems too demeaning to women.
鉴于你对女性的所作所为
Given the things you've done to women,
你这话说的有些随意了吧
that seems arbitrary.
你是朴克智  对吗
You're Chi Park, right?
你是谁
Who's asking?
你打过我吉他宣传弹上的电话
Uh, you called about my guitar flyer.
你是麦迦
You're Micah.
他卖的一款1974年烟草色吉布森SG吉他
This guy's selling a 1974 Gibson SG standard
吉普森吉他  美国知名乐器品牌
该款吉他属经典收藏款
开价只要1250美元
in tobacco for $1,250.
其实  我是来告诉你我已经把它卖了
Yeah, actually, I came in to tell you I already sold it.
抱歉
Sorry.
那也谢谢了
Thanks anyway.
血液化验结果同之前非常相近
Blood panel results seem pretty much the same as before,
还有刚才那人喜欢你
and that guy likes you.
也许我们应该检查一下糖尿病的指标
Maybe we should check for diabetes,
糖尿病可以导致结膜血管变弱
could weaken conjunctival vessels.
还有闭嘴
And shut up.
如果我说错了  那他为什么回来呢
If I'm wrong, then why is he coming back?
我们乐队明晚会彩排
My band is rehearsing tomorrow night.
你可以过来一起
You should come by and jam with us.
听上去不错
That...sounds fun.
我考虑考虑
I'll think about it.
太好了  回头打我电话
Great. Call me.
朴克有男友了
Park has a boyfriend.
小心我揍你
I'll break your face.
这是面试的才艺展示阶段
This is the talent portion of the interview.
好的
Okay.
你喜欢玩扑克
You like cards.
但你自己也能玩啊
But you can juggle.
我看不出她们这些对你有啥好处
I fail to see how this would be of benefit to you.
我要是没空玩呢
What if I'm busy?
还有什么绝活吗
Have you got anything else?
当然
Sure.
CT未显脑梗塞或血管畸形
CT showed no clots or malformations.
朴克和陶博已排除
Park and Taub ruled out
淋巴细胞增多症和糖尿病
lymphocytosis and diabetes.
要是你没什么可汇报的
Well, since you have nothing of relevance to report,
我就假设你是来加入她们的
I assume that you're here to toss your panties in the ring.
患者有一位神秘女友
Patient's got a mysterious girlfriend
他想见她
he really wants to see.
电话联系不上
She's unreachable by phone,
邻居也从未见过她
and the neighbor's never even seen her.
你怎么看
What do you think?
他是同性恋
He's gay.
我认为他是个瘾君子
I think he's a junkie.
女朋友只是幻想
The girlfriend is a fix.
他在吸毒
The guy's inhaling glue.
你会修搅拌机吗
Can you repair a blender?
不会修你能把我怎么样
Can you bite me?
去搜查患者的家
Go search the patient's home.
感谢两位
Well, thank you, ladies.
我见识了很多多才多艺的人
I've seen a lot of very talented candidates.
接下来就是艰难的选择了
Got a tough decision the next few days.
我最讨厌这个环节
This is the part I hate.
看起来也不像是个瘾君子的窝
Well...this is not exactly a crack den.
也不像是有女人居住的地方
Doesn't exactly look like a woman lives here, either.
"致艾米
"To amy.
"我爱你"
I love you."
好吧  她确实存在
Okay. She exists.
并不证明他没在吸毒啊
Doesn't mean he's not a drug addict.
你能冷静对待豪斯很好
It's good you're playing it cool with House.
他一但成功地把谁惹恼了...
Once he gets a rise out of someone...
我对招妓什么的虽然不怎么认同
Yeah, I'm not crazy about the whole hooker thing,
但是我懂
but I get it.
抛开这行业对于女性的欺压和危险不说
Other than the fact that it's exploitative and dangerous for women,
招妓行为本身既能满足自身需求
you get what you need
又不会背上感情包袱
without any of the emotional baggage.
看来你现在没男朋友吧
You're not seeing anyone, I take it.
我近来在特伦顿免费门诊做义工
I've been volunteering at the Trenton Free Clinic.
充实生活
Keeps me busy.
你每晚每个周末都在做义工吗
You volunteer every night and every weekend?
没时间出去吃顿饭
No time to grab dinner?
哪一个更重要
What's more important?
是吃着意式馄饨聊天
Making small talk over ravioli
还是帮助那些不幸的人们
or helping people who are less fortunate?
以你这样说  我们谁也别再吃饭了
With that rationale, none of us should ever eat again.
只能说我现在对吃东西没什么兴趣
Let's just say I'm not hungry right now.
天啊
Oh, god...
她好像停止呼吸了
I don't think she's breathing.
是不是吸毒过量了
Do you think she OD'd?
或是被他杀了
That or he killed her.
还有脉搏吗
Pulse?
没了
No.
我给验尸官打电话
I'll call the coroner.
我想没这个必要
I don't think that's gonna be necessary.
这位在金融界工作
This one works in financial district.
她能给你提供信息  在市场上给与你帮助
She can get tips, give you leg up in market.
什么是"冈萨雷斯巧克力"
What is "Fudgey Gonzalez"?
想象一下"冈萨雷斯香草"
Uh, imagine a "Vanilla Gonzalez,"
但是肤色不同
but from the other side.
我马上就要做出决定了
I'm about to make a decision,
但你现在加入还来得及
but there's still time for you to sneak under the wire.
我最喜爱的伍迪·艾伦电影是
My favorite Woody Allen movie
《双生美莲达》
is Melinda and Melinda.
患者并没在吸毒
Our patient is not a junkie,
但是他的确有个女朋友
but he does have a girlfriend.
我称她为女朋友是因为
I call her my "girlfriend"
其他人比较容易理解
because people understand that.
要是我解释了
If I explained it,
他们也只会觉得我很奇怪
they'd just think I was a weirdo.
我们不是来评判别人的癖好的
We're not here to judge anyone's fetish.
我不是变态
I'm not a pervert.
并不是说我喜欢充气娃娃胜过喜欢活生生的人
It's not like I'm more attracted to dolls than humans.
你没和她发生性关系吗
So you don't have sex with her?
这不仅仅是单纯的性关系
It's not just about that.
娃娃还和你聊天吗
Does the doll talk to you?
我知道她不是真人
I know she's not a real person.
很多方面来说  她比真人更好
In a lot of ways, she's better than a person.
我可以向她倾诉
I can tell her things,
她不会跟我争论  不会取笑我
and she won't argue with me or make fun of me.
我每晚回到家中
I come home every night,
都知道她会在家等着我
and I know she'll be there waiting.
你的面包机也在家等着呢
So is your toaster.
这世上没人会对面包机产生感情
No one in the world has an emotional attachment to a toaster.
但很多人会愿意花7000美金
But a lot of people are willing to spend $7,000
买一个像艾米这样的女人
on women like Amy.
你有试过和真人
Have you ever tried an actual--
有啊  我都35岁了
Yeah, I'm 35.
我谈过恋爱
I've been in relationships.
但是没有一段感情能让我心满意足的
None of them fulfilled me.
有一天  我发现了这个网站...
And one day, I saw this website, and...
也许我的真命天女确实存在
Maybe the perfect woman's out there somewhere,
但是花费很多精力去寻找她也一点不值得
but it's not worth going through what it would take to find her.
艾米让我很开心
Amy makes me happy.
-你的脸肿了  -这里挺热的
- You're swelling. - It's sort of hot in here.
也没你那么热
Not that hot.
出血加上两个新症状
Bleeding plus two more symptoms:
发热和神经系统症状
Fever and neurological.
我对后者不怎么确定
I'm not sure about that last one.
我觉得他只是有一点  奇怪
I think he's just...weird.
他没有产生幻觉
He wasn't hallucinating.
没有思维混乱
He didn't have a thought disorder.
你不觉得和充气娃娃谈话是
And you don't think it's "disordered" to talk to--
其实这和跟猫跟玩具熊说话没什么区别
It's not all that different from talking to your cat or a teddy bear.
可你不会和你的猫或玩具熊搞上啊
You don't have sex with your cat or teddy bear.
要是你搞上了
If you did,
说不定会和它们聊得更欢
you'd probably talk to them more.
这家伙爱上了一个虚拟情人
Guy loves an imaginary being
一个永远不会作出任何回应的东西
who's never going to respond to him.
也就跟百万教徒一般疯狂
He's no crazier than millions of churchgoers.
你一直以为
You think anything off
患者有任何的不对劲都是一种症状
about any patient is a symptom.
这家伙买了鲜花
This guy buys flowers.
为一个穿着裙子的塑料人买鲜花
Real flowers for a piece of plastic in a dress.
你知道什么事更荒唐吗
You know what's really crazy?
和活生生的人住在一起
Living with a human being.
一个有主见有感情的人
Someone with opinions and feelings.
就因为你想每周和她去上一堂
Gets mad just 'cause you want to take Salsa classes
萨尔萨舞课  她就闹脾气
with them one night a week.
每周就一次
One night.
他只是在逃避
He's just running away.
和一个充气娃娃过日子
He hangs out with a doll,
就永远不用担心会被拒绝
he never needs to fear rejection.
真是凄惨
It's sad.
你们知道最讽刺的是什么吗
You do understand the irony here?
这屋里的所有人都有个充气娃娃
Every person in this room has a sex doll.
至少这患者还有胆承认
At least the patient has the stones to be honest about it.
打的比喻是吧
Ooh, a metaphor.
你没想到的是
What you didn't foresee is that
我还真的有一个
I actually do have a sex doll.
你的娃娃是你两个孩子
Your doll is your kids.
你的是你父母
Yours is your parents,
你的是慈善机构
Yours is your charity.
这些都是你们不谈恋爱的借口
All excuses for not being in a relationship.
他说的没错
He's not wrong.
-还有你  -我随意和陌生人上床
- And you-- - I have meaningless sex with random strangers.
谢谢你分享见解
Thanks for the insight,
但我几个月前就不再那样了
but I stopped that months ago.
还谈了一场恋爱
I actually had a relationship.
和一位患者
With a patient.
谁从你门前过你就和谁约会
You just date whoever happens to cross your path.
你是说我的恋爱阻碍了我的爱情生活吗
My dating is getting in the way of my dating?
你从不认真去找个适合你的人
You don't go looking for the right person.
随便拉个人就能同居
You just shack up with whoever's in the room,
之后出点状况
and then you get surprised and/or divorced
不是倍感吃惊就是离婚收场
when it doesn't work out.
真惊讶你到现在都还没约亚当斯出去
I'm surprised you haven't asked Adams out yet.
知会你一声
Uh, for your information,
今晚我要去约会了
I've got a date tonight.
和一小帅哥还有他的乐队
I'll be jamming with a cute guy and his band.
-你会放鸽子  -没错
- You'll bail. - He's right.
最明智的做法  就是让你父母帮我带孩子
The obvious solution is for me to hand my kids over to your parents.
我们能停止这类争论
Can we stop trying to argue the premise
想想为什么
and move onto figuring out
你们都是些社交白痴吗
why it is that you're all social morons?
你不觉得这很讽刺吗
You do understand the irony here.
你嘲笑我们回避感情
You mocking us for avoiding relationships,
自己却无法忍受失去你的"娃娃"
but you can't handle losing your "Doll."
所以才花这么多时间精力
Your spending all this time and energy
就为找一个新的
interviewing for a new one.
你说得对  这太蠢了
You're right. That is stupid.
病人怎么说
What about the patient?
这人和充气娃娃搞上了
Dude's banging a sex doll.
那货无异于一个充满体液和细菌的污水池
A festering cesspool of bodily fluids and associated bacteria.
从她体内取些标本化验下  看看是什么细菌
Swab her out and find out which one.
我需要你
I need you.
不要退隐江湖
Please don't quit.
你是我认识的唯一一个会弹钢琴的妓女
You're the only hooker I know who can tune a piano.
如果是钱的问题
If it's about the money,
我可以每周叫你三个晚上
then I can up you to three nights a week.
我要结婚了  豪斯
I'm getting married, House.
他叫哈里斯
His name's Harris.
是名注册会计师
He's a certified accountant,
喜欢蹩脚的恐怖电影
he loves schlocky horror movies,
刚和我搬到一起住
and he just moved in.
我们很幸福
We're very happy.
你们很幸福
Well, you're happy?
是因为他不知道
Yeah, you're happy because he doesn't know
你之前的职业经历吧
about your employment history.
他知道
He knows.
我们谈过
We've talked about it,
他接受了这样的我
and he accepts me for who I am.
不  他
No. He...
如果他接受这样的你
If he accepted who you were,
就不会让你放弃你的事业
he would not be making you give up your career.
女人要有自己的个性
Women need their own identities,
自己的营生
their own livelihoods.
不然为什么我还在抽女士烟呢
Otherwise, why was I smoking all those virginia slims?
我知道这对你来说很奇怪
I know this is weird for you,
但你要试着去接受
but you need to figure out a way to be okay with it.
我也会想你的
I'll miss you, too.
把她放妇科检查台上也太过了
I feel like the stirrups are overkill.
我之前没查过充气娃娃
I've never done a pelvic on a doll before.
对流程不是很熟悉
I'm unfamiliar with the protocol.
现在  我感觉是挺诡异的
I'm pretty skeeved out right now.
这点不假
I'm not gonna lie.
豪斯之前说的
What House said back there--
之前豪斯说了很多话
House says a lot of things.
我不是见一个爱一个的
I don't just date whoever shows up.
我的确是把过在医院认识的姑娘
I mean, I did meet women in the hospital,
但我并不只是玩玩的
but they weren't just flings.
基本上  你是在解释为什么你不约我出去
Basically, you're explaining why you're not going to ask me out.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I was--
你想让我约你出去吗
Did you want me to ask you out?
是啊
Yeah.
我让朴克去告诉陶博
I told Park to tell Taub
转告豪斯向你透露我是这么想的
to tell House to pass you that note.
里面非常干净
It's completely clean in there.
他说了他刚给她洗过澡
He said he just bathed her.
亚当斯...
Adams...
皮下有一处凸起
There's a swelling beneath the skin...
三英寸大小
3-inch mass.
会不会是
Is it...
娃娃骨架的一部分
part of the doll's skeleton?
摸上去像肿瘤
It feels like a tumor.
CT显示娃娃腹部有一处气泡
CT showed an air-filled mass in the doll's abdomen.
可能只是化学反应
It's probably just a chemical reaction.
可能亨利把她放得离暖气管太近了
Henry left her too close to a heating pipe or something.
这人每天早上给她梳头发
This guy brushes her hair every morning,
带影片回家和她一起看
brings home movies for them to watch together.
你觉得晚上他会把她和扫帚一起
You think he tosses her in a broom closet
扔进柜子里吗
at the end of each day?
这总比说它得了胃癌来的靠谱
More likely than it getting stomach cancer.
会不会是梭状芽胞杆菌
How about clostridium?
杆菌被困在密闭腔内
Bacteria got trapped in the airtight cavity,
代谢出气体
produced gas...
它不能解释神经系统的问题
It doesn't explain the neurological issue.
我们就是这样
We can explain that the same way
解释牙仙的
we explain the tooth fairy.
我要去演所罗门王
Oh, I get to play Solomon.
去把充气娃娃切开
Cut the doll open.
我们不能就这样破坏病人的财产
We can't just destroy the patient's property.
那东西值七千美金呢
That thing cost 7 grand.
没错  问问他同不同意
Exactly. Ask him for consent.
如果他说同意
If he says yes,
那我们就开始找芽孢杆菌
then we get to go hunting bacteria.
他不同意  说明他疯了  也不用找杆菌了
If he says no, there's no need because he's crazy,
我们就要另找病因了
And we need a different theory.
再见啦
See ya.
得去搭一座庙了
Gotta go build a temple.
好吧
Okay.
你确定吗
You sure?
切开之后可就修不好了
It won't be able to heal when we're done.
但你们觉得她能告诉你们我究竟怎么了
But you think she could tell you what's wrong with me.
是的
Yes.
好吧
Okay.
我们不把她推到手术室吗
Should we take her to the procedure room?
她不是人  所以我们在哪里手术都行
It's not a her, which means we can do this anywhere.
亚当斯
Adams...
有时你知道有些东西虽然不是真实的
You can know something's not real
但你仍然爱它
and still love it.
去手术室进行也许更好一点
I think the procedure room might be better for this.
你真的太坏了
You are a horrible person.
我只想要破坏一次婚姻
All I need is to break up one marriage.
你都已经毁了三次你自己的婚姻了
You've broken up three of your own.
你就像离婚界的斯蒂芬·霍金
You're like the Stephen Hawking of killing relationships.
不  实际上他算是...
Actually, no, Stephen Hawking is the Stephen Hawking of--
行了  我有事要做
Okay. I have work to do.
你电脑没开
Your computer is off.
对不起  音响太大声  听不见你讲话
Sorry, I can't hear you over my "Stereo."
你凭什么认为婚姻比招妓好
Why do you assume that marriage is better than hooking?
我们对他完全不了解
We don't know anything about the guy.
可能是个连环杀手呢
He could be a serial killer.
即使真有这事
Even if that were true,
这两者的优劣还有待商讨
it would still be a toss-up.
什么人会愿意娶一个妓女
What kind of guy marries a hooker?
招妓的人
Somebody who hires hookers.
但招妓的人
And someone who hires hookers
不是那种专一的类型
is not exactly the monogamous type.
如果我们揭露他的本性
If we expose him as a cheater...
你是个胆小鬼
You're a coward.
你见过哪个胆小鬼奋战到底挽救少女
Would a coward fight to the end
于即将被证实的痛苦绝望之境吗
to save a damsel in soon-to-be-proved distress?
当然  如果他怕的是其他的少女的话
Absolutely, if what he's afraid of is other damsels.
你上一次的恋情结局太惨
Your last relationship failed so miserably,
你进了监狱
you ended up in jail.
所以现在你把妓女当做寄托
Now you're clinging to this hooker
虽然还有大约30亿的
when there are about 3 billion other women out there
非妓女在这世上
who aren't call girls,
其中不乏迷人聪颖的
some of whom are attractive and intelligent,
其中一个还住在你的公寓里
one of whom is living in your apartment
还和你结婚了
and is married to you!
你说得对
You're right.
我来找你帮什么忙
Why am I asking you for help?
你不该和奇斯上床
You shouldn't sleep with Chase.
谢天谢地  你来得真及时
Thank, god. You got here just in time.
你反感他什么
What do you have against him?
没什么  只是豪斯对洗脑有一手
Nothing, but House has a way of getting into people's heads.
就像上周
Just like last week
他刺探你和奇斯之间那样
when he was prying into your relationship with Chase?
那是件蠢事  现在也是
It was silly then, and it's silly now.
为什么说那是件蠢事
Why was it silly then?
我没有高挑的身材  卷卷的长发
I'm not 5'9" With curves and flowing hair,
所以我就不可能
so it's impossible for me to get it on
和帅哥在一起吗
with a good-looking guy?
你在怨我吗
Wow. Do you resent me?
就好像你是奇怪的努力学习的大二学生
You're the quirky, hardworking sophomore
而我是专偷男生的邪恶啦啦队长一样
and I'm the evil cheerleader who steals boys?
你没男朋友可不是我的错
If you're not getting any, it's not my fault.
我们应该买上面有熊猫的还是有鸟的呢
Should we get the one with the panda on it or the bird?
选的好
Good choice.
熊猫只吃竹子
Pandas eat only bamboo,
他们不懂麦片
they know nothing about cereal.
你的小女儿太可爱了
Your little girl is adorable.
谢谢
Thanks.
她让我忙坏了
She keeps me very busy.
你和她母亲一定很自豪
You and her mom must be very proud.
她母亲...分娩时去世了
Her mother... died in childbirth.
艾米
Amy.
情况怎么样
How'd it go?
我们正在进行组织培养
We're growing cultures now,
不过她看上去很干净  也没有明显的味道
but she looked clean, and there was no telltale smell.
我猜那肿块只是成型时
I'm guessing the lump was just an air bubble
困在里面的气泡
that got trapped in the mold.
你还给她上了绷带
You bandaged her up.
我还给她缝了几针
I threw in some stitches, too.
只是希望她看起来最好
Just wanted to make her look her best.
需要我把她放在椅子上吗
Do you want me to put her in her chair?
亨利
Henry?
叫急救
Call a code!
你是在看人家的房间
You looking at the apartment with those
还是在看温度计的变化
or the transit of mercury?
到了晚上你会感谢我的
If night comes, you'll be thanking me.
他们正在找暖气
They're seeking heat.
他是名会计
He's an accountant.
你觉得他多晚才会去参加派对
How late do you think he's going to party?
我买了罐子来撒尿
I bought jar to pee in.
说吧
Yeah.
我们在亨利的肺里听到湿罗音
We heard crackles in Henry's lungs.
我们给他用了利尿药  但他仍然需要氧气
We diuresed him, but he still needs oxygen.
超声心电图显示心功能正常
Echo shows normal heart function.
可能是贫血导致的高输出衰竭
Could be high output failure from anemia.
红细胞压积没有任何问题
Hematocrit was rock normal.
这是什么  蘑菇吗
What is this? Mushroom?
说蘑菇  两块
Say "Mushroom," charge $2.
说松露  五块
Say "Truffle," charge $5.
那就是那个想娶个妓女的男人吗
Is that the man who wants to marry hooker?
可能吧
Probably.
但他不是我们要跟踪的对象
But he's not the one we're after.
我们该提问吗
Should we ask?
不
Nope.
让你们等着实在是太无理了
How rude of me not to situate you.
我正在帮艾米丽的忙
I'm doing Emily a favor.
我们正在跟踪她的未婚夫
We're going to track her fiance
直到多米尼卡能成功引诱并让他暴露
until Dominika can seduce and expose him
我需要的他骗子的本性
as the lying cheater I need him to be.
我估计她并没让你帮这个忙
I'm guessing she didn't ask for this favor.
要知道最高贵的礼物
Oh, you know, the noblest gifts
都是我们匿名送出的
are the ones we give anonymously.
湿罗音是非特异性的
Crackles are nonspecific.
组织缺氧和出血可能是弥漫性血管内凝血
Hypoxia plus bleeding could indicate D.I.C.
或其它
Or some other--
没有神经系统症状吗
No neurological symptoms?
我知道你那颗流血的心让你内心复苏了
I knew your bleeding heart would bring you around.
很遗憾也使你失去了市场
Too bad it's also taking you off the market.
我说的市场指的是奇斯
And by market, I mean Chase.
快点  加把劲  奇斯
Come on, buck up, Chase.
虽然总会有朴克   除非...
There's always Park. Unless...
乐队的训练进行的如何
How did band practice go?
-很好  -她看上去像是在撒谎吗
- Great. - Does she look like she's lying?
有点
Kind of.
姥姥需要人陪去看医生
Popo needed a ride to the doctor,
我妈没空所以...
and my mom couldn't, so--
你害怕和某人约会因为...
You're terrified of dating because...
你上一段感情之所以结束是因为
a previous relationship ended because your latent rage
你隐藏的愤怒使你在争吵中变得十分恶毒
made you vicious in arguments.
-或者  -或者是因为转世
- Or-- - Or reincarnation.
上辈子她是安·波林
In a past life, she was Anne Boleyn.
有意思
Interesting.
陶博有足够的自信
Taub feels confident enough
把枪口转向自己
to turn the spotlight on himself.
这几乎是肯定希望我问他...
It's almost as if he wants me to ask...
她叫什么
What's her name?
温迪·亚克布森
Wendy Jacobson.
33岁  布朗大学毕业  家庭治疗师
33, Brown grad, family therapist.
不错的选择
Nice choice.
考虑到你已经有两个家庭需要被治疗了
Since you got two families to "Therapize."
初次约会
First date,
我们并没把所有重要的事都讨论过来
we didn't discuss everything important--
这么说是一夜情了
So it was just a one-night stand.
你错了  我挺喜欢她的
You're wrong. I actually like her.
我还要再约她出来
I'm going to see her again.
恭喜
Mazel tov.
一段成功感情的开始往往源于希望证明
Great relationships often start with snap decisions
我是错的这类草率的决定
aimed at proving me wrong.
娃娃里的气泡可能意味着硅胶降解了
Air bubble in the doll could mean the silicone is degrading.
如果他粘上了一些颗粒...
If he hailed some particles...
硅胶沉积
Silicone deposition.
很有可能
That could work.
给他进行血浆过滤治疗
Start him on plasmapheresis.
现在  回到亚当斯的问题
Now, turning to Adams,
我的理论分为三部分...
My theory is tripartite--
想听听我的论点吗
Want to hear my thesis?
挺有意思的
It's kind of interesting.
没有男人出来
No man comes out.
不过3C房间有个全裸的大妈正在吃一大块奶酪
But old naked lady in 3-C is eating whole block of cheese.
这会疼吗
Will this hurt?
不  不过你可能会觉得有点凉
No, you might feel a little cold, though.
该死
Crap.
我只有一点时间
I only have a second,
不过我刚去听了个时间旅行的讲座
but I went to the time travel lecture.
那真是...太棒了
That is...awesome.
这是什么
What is it?
这太...
It's so...
跟真的似的
Oh, realistic.
还绑了绷带
Oh, and it's all bandaged up.
这是用来练习心肺复苏的吗
It is one of those CPR things?
不
No.
我们要开始进行一些治疗
We're starting a procedure.
-需要一点私人空间  -不不...
- A little privacy-- - No, no, it's--
她在这挺好
it's good that she's here.
莫莉
Molly,
见过艾米
I'd like you to meet Amy.
什么
What?
我是认真的
I'm serious.
我知道这看上去有点奇怪
I know it seems a little strange,
但她对我很重要
but she means a lot to me.
我得回去工作了
I, um, got to get back to work.
但你才刚来  坐会儿
But you just got here. Sit down.
是啊  但我...
Yeah, but I--
我说过我只有一点时间
I said that I only had a second.
你可以看看讲义
Enjoy the handouts.
听着  我得坦白一些事情
Listen, um, I have to admit something.
好吧
Okay.
她妈妈还活着
Her mom isn't dead.
我们分手了
We're separated.
你是自那以后我约的第一个人
You're the first person I've asked out since then.
我不知道该怎么解释  当时口不择言
I'm not used to explaining... I panicked.
我现在后悔了  因为认识你以后
Which I regret, because now that I've gotten to know you,
我挺喜欢你的
I like you.
真不该乱扯谎
It was a really stupid lie.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这是另一个婴儿吗
Was that a different baby?
不是
No...
还真是另一个婴儿啊
That was a different baby.
有你在这里陪我真好
It's nice having you here.
真希望你能过来陪我在床上待着
I wish you could come over and get in bed with me.
像这样吗
Like this?
你竟然能说话
You're talking?
我还能做很多事呢
It's not all I can do.
艾米  外面有医生
Amy, there are doctors...
我不知道怎么做好
I don't know.
把你的手放上来
Just put your hands on me.
好疼
It hurts.
推注劳拉西泮
Pushing lorazepam.
如果之前不是神经系统症状的话  现在肯定是了
If it wasn't neurological before, it sure is now.
右上腹部膨隆
Right upper quadrant's distended.
他会产生幻觉是因为他肝脏衰竭了
He's hallucinating because his liver's failing.
转氨酶升高证实了肝衰竭
Elevated transaminases confirm liver failure.
用不了几天他的名字就该上移植手术名单了
We'll have to put him on the transplant list in a couple days.
这显然不是硅酮  可能是血管炎
It's clearly not the silicone. Could be vasculitis.
血清学检测结果呈阴性
Serologies were negative.
我说  如果你想让亚当斯听见[听取意见]
Yeah, if you want Adams to hear,
就别站那么远说话[就别直接否定她]
you might want to not stand so conspicuously far away.
我在煮咖啡
I'm making coffee.
偶尔地  我是会跟同事约会
And sometimes, I date co-workers.
地球人都一样
Like everyone else on the planet.
肝硬化
Hepatic fibrosis.
如果肝硬化破坏了他的血小板
If it damaged his platelets,
就能解释出血症状
it'd explain the bleeding.
出人意料
Unexpected.
我还以为你会同意我的观点呢
I actually thought you might agree with my theory.
那就表示你什么错都没有
Because that would mean nothing's your fault.
人们因为近距离接触而发展关系
You fell into relationships based on proximity.
当然肯定长久不了
Of course they failed.
看来是我错了
But I guess I was wrong.
你选对了人  却搞砸了
You picked perfect women. You just screwed it up.
我们五个人住一起
How about all five of us live together
外加一个7000美元的充气娃娃  怎样
and the $7,000 sex doll?
所有的包袱一概解决了
It'll solve all our hang-ups.
7000美元
$7,000?
亚当斯建议我们一起睡
Adams suggests that we all sleep together,
你却在乎娃娃的价格
and your issue is high prices?
我确信她那是玩笑话
Pretty sure she was joking.
我也几乎相信你说得没错
Yes, I'm 99% sure that you're right,
但我不会原谅自己
but I would never forgive myself--
那娃娃售价5000
Those dolls are only $5,000.
他肯定是依个人喜好定制的
He must have had it customized somehow.
别一副你们没上网看过的样子
Oh, like, you didn't check the website?
看来我们不必多嘴问你约会如何了
I guess we don't need to ask how your dating life is going.
好奇而已
I was curious.
肝硬化不会导致呼吸困难
Hepatic fibrosis wouldn't cause difficulty breathing.
如果肝衰竭导致了肺部动静脉分流的话就有可能
It would if liver failure opened pulmonary av shunts.
肝硬化符合病症  给病人用类固醇
Fibrosis fits. Start the patient on steroids
弄清楚他是怎么定制他的坐骑的
and find out how he pimped his ride.
为什么
Why?
好奇而已嘛
Because I don't know the answer.
玩桌上足球吗
Foosball?
没空  有婚姻要破坏
Can't. Marriage to destroy.
好的吧
Okay...
欲擒故纵逆反心理的"好吧"
"Okay" as in passive-aggressive reverse psychology?
还是逆来顺受的"好吧"
Or as in depressed resignation
我改变主意的意思
"Okay" as in I changed my mind.
也就是
Expand.
破坏他人幸福应受道义谴责且注定失败
Oh, it's morally reprehensible and bound to fail,
但怎么说起来  你都是向前迈了一步
but in a weird way, it's a step forward.
就艾米丽的事情而言
This thing with Emily.
也就是说
Contract.
虚假才是真实
It's real without being real.
这样的长久关系伤不到你
It's a long-term relationship that can't actually hurt you.
这是  一块踏脚石
It's, um...A stepping stone.
说明你想要更多
It means you want more.
看来是欲擒故纵逆反心理
So, passive-aggressive reverse psychology.
懂了
Got it.
别太直白了
Try not to come on too strong, okay?
稍微打探一下  顺势切入主题
Just get to know him a little. Ease into it.
我为什么要慢慢来
Why would I ease?
也对
True.
你可以大步流星走过去直接海底捞月
You could just walk up and stick your hand down his pants,
但好像漏掉了些步骤
but I heard there's a middle step.
男人都想做爱
Men want to have sex.
对象不能是怪人
Not with crazy people.
好吧  很多男人会跟怪人做
Well, yes, a lot with crazy people,
但不是疯子
but not that kind of crazy.
好吧  也是有选疯子的
Well, yeah, that kind of crazy--
有我这般姿色的他们才不在乎是不是疯子呢
They don't care how crazy if she look like me.
好了  放轻松
Okay. Easing.
我叫詹妮弗  市场部新来的
I'm Jennifer, new to marketing department.
我是哈里斯  应收账款会计
Harris. Accounts receivable.
有意思
Oh, interesting.
想到别处去做爱吗
Do you want to get out of here and have sex?
好啊
Uh, sure.
我午餐时间还剩45分钟
You know, I got 45 minutes left on my lunch break.
-好的  -你想去哪里
- Mm-hmm. - Where you wanna go?
去一个男人不会背叛自己爱妻的地方
Off to a place where men don't cheat on the women they love.
你明显是去不成了
You're not invited, obviously.
背叛  你说什么呢
Cheating? What are you talking about?
我希望你现在说的话
Why, I hope you're speaking
是出于深层次的道德相对主义  因为
out of some deep kind of moral relativism because--
你们是什么人啊
Who are you people?
你不是艾米丽的未婚夫
You're not Emily's fiance.
艾米丽是我妹妹
Emily's my sister.
我们联系了艾米的制造商
We called the company that made Amy.
他们说是根据你提供的照片定制的
They said they modeled her after some photos you sent them.
她是谁
Who is she?
去年圣诞节的时候认识的
We met last christmas.
她是名瑜珈教练
She's a yoga instructor.
跟我完全不是一类人
Totally different from me.
她喜欢肖邦  讨厌印度菜
She--she loved Chopin, hated Indian food.
那17周她彻底改变了我的生活
She changed entire my life for 17 weeks.
我丈夫背叛了我
My husband cheated on me...
和从我们蜜月归来的飞机上认识的女孩
With a girl he met on the plane coming back from our honeymoon.
这种事情很难让人释怀
It's not easy to get past things like that.
不是她不忠  她没有背叛我
She wasn't unfaithful. She didn't betray me.
她根本  就不爱我
She just...she just wasn't in love with me.
我明白艾米不会伤你的心
I know Amy's not going to break your heart.
但她也不能改变你的生活
But she's also not going to change your life.
灯光好刺眼
The lights are bright.
抱歉  我这是怎么了
Sorry. What's happening to me?
你脖子硬吗
Is your neck stiff?
是的
Yeah.
我想你得了脑膜炎
I think you have meningitis.
我没有要离开这个行业
I'm not leaving the business.
只是要  离开你
I'm just leaving you.
我不想让你伤心
I didn't want you to feel bad.
那我来帮你理顺这意思
So let me get this straight.
我被一个妓女给甩了
I'm being dumped by a hooker...
她还在乎我的感受
Who's worried about my feelings?
你已婚了
You're married.
你半数的客人都是已婚
Half your clients are married.
何况你是个妓女
And you're a hooker.
我的其他客人会在外面搞
My other guys sneak around,
你直接带我登堂入室
but you'll take me into the bedroom
而你老婆就在隔壁
while your wife's in the next room.
实在是  太过分了
That's just...mean.
上帝啊
Oh, my god.
这个婚姻就是个幌子
The marriage, it's a sham.
唯一真实的就是婚姻结束时
The only really thing about it is the green card
她要拿到的那张绿卡
she's going to get at the end of it.
所以如果你乐意重启进程...
So, if you want to get the meter running...
还是很过分
It's still mean.
这不是婚姻  这是罔顾法度
It's not a marriage. It's a felony.
我见过你们在一起时她看你的样子
I've seen how she looks at you when you're together.
相信我
Trust me.
她喜欢你
She likes you.
我也见过你看她的样子
And I've seen how you look at her.
发热达到40.5度  他对药物没有反应
Fever's up 105. He's not responding to meds.
照这样发展下去
At this rate, he'll be dead
没等我们拿到培养结果他就死了
by the time we get the cultures back.
脑脊液里面充满了白色细胞
Spinal fluid was full of white cells.
脑膜炎可能是癌性的
Meningitis could be carcinomatous.
细胞学检查没有异常
Cytology showed nothing.
阿米巴感染应该引起发热和脑膜炎
An amoebic infection would cause fever and meningitis.
但不会引起肝衰竭
But not liver failure.
如果他发生了血栓就有可能
It could if he had a clot.
阿米巴原虫怎么可能通过他的筛板呢
How could amoebas get past his cribriform plate?
他跑去新泽西州冰冻的湖泊里游泳了吗
He went swimming in a frozen lake in New Jersey?
亚当斯说他前女友是瑜伽教练
Adams said his ex-girlfriend was a yoga instructor.
说不定他扭伤了脉轮
Maybe he sprained his chakras.
瑜伽爱好者容易尝试另类疗法
Yoga nuts are way more likely to be into alternative medicine.
他家有只怪怪的小茶壶
He has this little weird teapot in his house.
什么样的
What was it like?
就是  小小的  怪怪的  茶壶样
Um, little. Weird. Teapot-ish.
像这样吗
Like that?
对
Yeah.
你认为他喝了有毒的花草茶
You think he drinks some sort of toxic herbal tea?
没错
Yes...
如果你所说的"茶"指的是加盐的自来水
If by "tea," you mean salted tap water.
"喝"指的是灌进鼻腔
And by "drink," you mean poured up his nose.
前女友不仅留给他一颗破碎的心
His girlfriend didn't just leave him with a broken heart.
还留下一只鼻壶
She left him with a neti pot.
是种印度疗法
It's an Indian method of
用于在过敏季节清洗鼻窦
clearing the sinuses during allergy season.
现在正是过敏季节
Also known as now.
蒸馏水可以用作鼻涕冲洗
The distilled water can act as a snot flushing system.
而自来水  就相当于通向脑脊液
With tap water, it can act as an amoeba delivery system
的阿米巴运输系统
to the fluids around the brain.
给他用甲硝唑
Start him on metronidazole.
如果他命好
If he's lucky, he'll get to see
可以活到看着他的假人子女成家立业呢
his plastic children walk down the aisle.
我的脖子感觉好多了
My neck feels much better.
你退烧了
Your fever's gone,
肝功能也回到了正常水平
and your liver function's almost back to normal.
应该很快就可以回家了
You should be able to go home soon.
我有一笔住院费用要付了
I'm going to have some hospital bills to pay.
二手性爱玩偶在网上恐怕买不了多少钱
I don't suppose used sex dolls go for anything online.
亚当斯医生
Dr. Adams?
能给我你的邮件地址吗
Can I get your email?
做什么用
What for?
我只是想  我们或许可以再见面
I just thought maybe we could see each other again.
这  不好吧
I...I can't.
我明白  这是职业要求
No, I know. It's a professionalism thing,
可我出院后你就不是我的医生了
But you won't be my doctor when I get out of here.
不是那样  是...
It's not that. It's...
是什么呢
What is it?
你说我应该改变生活
You said I should change my life.
其实你也想改变
You were talking about yourself, too.
-我知道的  -亨利  我...
- I know you were. - Henry, I...
我认为你该约莫莉出去
I think you should ask Molly out.
我早该知道会这样
I should have known this would happen.
亨利  你是个好人
You're a good guy, Henry.
不该终日跟玩偶相伴
You deserve more than a doll.
答应我不要放弃
Promise me you'll keep trying.
好的
Okay.
今晚有约吗
Date tonight?
她接受不了
So she can't deal.
自然还是有人能接受
There's someone out there who can.
遇到就好啦
You just got to find her.
我也想证明豪斯是错的
I'd love to prove House wrong,
可是  是我毁了自己的婚姻
but... I ruined my marriage,
伤了两个人的心
broke two people's hearts,
生了两个孩子  他们从小到大都会在想
had two kids who are always
我当初为什么不够爱她妈妈
going to wonder why I didn't love their mommy enough.
我还是...  珍惜眼前比较好
It's better if I just... focus on what I do have.
打电话给乐队那小子
Give that band guy a call.
我吉他弹得不怎么好
I'm not that good at guitar.
调情不会  闲聊糟糕
Or flirting or small talk.
也没有亚当斯漂亮
I'm not as pretty as Adams,
穿的像个民工  发型也衰到家
I have stuffy clothes, and I hate my hair.
亚当斯一周花80小时帮流浪汉医腱膜
Adams works 80 hours a week fixing bunions on hobos
因为她不敢结识新面孔
because she can't face getting to know someone new.
相信我
Trust me.
等你找到男朋友  就换她嫉妒你了
You find a boyfriend, she'll be the jealous one.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
你想不想
Do you...
出去喝一杯
want to get a drink?
为了气朴克  还是为了证明豪斯是错的
To annoy Park or to prove House wrong?
我...  至少...
Oh, I... it's just, um...
我想是时候该作出改变了
I think it's time for a change.
我觉得现在很好
I don't really think that's a good idea for me right now.
豪斯总有办法给人洗脑
House has a way of getting in people's heads.
-是啊  -是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
不是啦  妈  我还在工作
No, mom. I'm still at work.
过几个小时就回家
I'll be home in a couple hours.
我也爱你
Love you too.
好了吗
Ready?
一  二  三 四
One, two, three, four.
我把搅拌器修好了
I fix blender.
我看到了
So I see.
色诱妓女的假未婚夫我很开心
I had fun seducing hooker's fake fiance.
没管用太遗憾了
Sorry it didn't work.
是啊  妓女这事我想暂时告一段落
Yeah, I thought I'd take a break from the whole hooker thing.
我想你或许需要奶昔
I think maybe you need milk shake.
加开心果仁的哦
Is pistachio.
我去睡了  明天见
I'm...gonna go to bed. See you tomorrow.